=In Love With Loving You=
(Based on Love by Erxi on Qimao)
=Episode 5=
ظآزA hurried encounterظآز
ظآزThat one glance backظآز
ظآزHeld infinite tendernessظآز
ظآزAt the night crossroadsظآز
ظآزThrough the flowing trafficظآز
Ji Xuan.
Is Xiao Jin your first love?
ظآزAfter holding youظآز
ظآزKissing your foreheadظآز
ظآزAfraid the wait is too longظآز
ظآزWaiting by your sideظآز
ظآزHaven't loved enoughظآز
ظآزAll of itظآز
First loves are unforgettable, right?
Mr. Song.
We agreed we would only discuss work.
You haven't answered me
about whether we're continuing the game.
Mr. Song.
It was just a slip of the tongue.
I can't afford it.
I remember you used to be quite wild.
ظآزWe promised never to partظآز
ظآزIn the quiet nightظآز
At 10:00 PM,
hotel front desk.
I prepared a gift for you.
Song Zhaoli of the Song Group
dates with a beauty tonight?
What I heard isn't just that.
Most shockingly,
he dates with two women!
That shocking?
For real?
We must get good shots.
- He's here.
Mr. Song, please tell us more.
Mr. Song,
is it really like the rumors say?
Tell us more, Mr. Song.
- Mr. Song, tell us more.
- Please tell us.
- Mr. Xiao!
- Mr. Xiao is here!
Tell us more.
Mr. Xiao, tell us.
Xiao Jin is really tricky to deal with.
He's about to get married,
yet still secret dating
with his boss's wife in a hotel?
- When?
- Saturday.
Right at the hot spring hotel.
Liao Bei.
Find me two beautiful women.
Stop filming!
Please tell us.
- How long have you two been together?
- Stop filming!
Mr. Xiao.
Let's go.
Don't go, Mr. Xiao.
Mr. Xiao!
I just saw Xiao Jin secretly
take two pills in the restroom.
He's a man
who needs pills for an affair.
You better think carefully
if he's worth entrusting your life to.
So many media outlets
are exposing your scandal.
If I hadn't stepped in in time,
you would've completely
disgraced the Song family.
I'm not the only one disgraced.
So was Mr. Xiao of Rongsheng Group.
Why implicate others?
Go apologize to the Xie family now.
I said I won't marry
someone I don't like.
You have no choice.
The marriage alliance
between the Xie and Song families
was settled long ago.
If Shaoqian hadn't died unjustly,
this marriage wouldn't
even be falling to you.
Grandpa.
Either break off the engagement,
or just beat me to death,
turning a wedding into a funeral.
Outrageous!
I'm telling you this.
Even if you die,
you have to marry first!
- Mom.
- You're back.
What brings you here?
Didn't you say you were returning
from a business trip today?
I made you some soup.
Xuan.
Here, drink it while it's hot.
You're here?
Xiao Jin said he hadn't seen you
in a long time.
It's perfect timing today.
Let's discuss your wedding.
Come on.
Xuan, please stop being angry.
No matter what, it's all my fault.
Forgive me, okay?
Mom, Xiao Jin and I broke up.
The wedding is canceled.
What did you say?
It's nothing.
We just had a small dispute
about the wedding.
We're making up soon.
Mom, Xiao Jin had an affair
with his boss's wife.
We agreed he would message you first
and tell you the wedding was postponed,
and then I'd tell you.
But now his scandal
with the boss's wife is exposed,
so he's desperate to use our wedding
to quell the scandal.
Am I right?
Didn't you also get caught in
a scandal with another man?
Marriage is about
mutual benefit, after all.
After we marry, you cover for me,
and in return,
I'll pay off all your debts.
Any problem?
Outrageous!
What are you saying?
Get lost!
Didn't expect you are so despicable.
Take your things.
Get out!
Xuan would rather stay single
than marry you!
Get lost!
Mom, I'm fine.
Xuan.
All these years, you've had it tough
paying off your father's debts.
I thought that once you got married,
things would get better.
I never thought Xiao Jin
would be such a person.
How dare he!
It's okay, Mom.
Really?
That's good then.
By the way, who's the man
Xiao Jin mentioned?
That's my new boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Good.
So when are you bringing him home
for me to meet?
This time, I will definitely
vet him properly for you.
(Wu Shu)
- Hello?
- Xuan.
About Xiao Jin being exposed
by the media, let me tell you the truth.
I heard Song Zhaoli deliberately
found two beautiful women.
They never even entered the hotel room.
(I heard Song Zhaoli deliberately
found two beautiful women.)
(They never even
entered the hotel room.)
(I always thought we were just
playing a game between adults.)
(Why would he do all this for me?)
Mr. Song.
I...
Why are you here?
Mr. Song.
You are running a fever.
Let me help you inside.
Easy now.
ظآزFlickering neon lightsظآز
What happened?
Wait a second.
ظآزMy heartbeat for youظآز
ظآزWant to ride the evening breezeظآز
Bear with it.
ظآزThe starry sky is like your eyesظآز
ظآزIn the blue skyظآز
ظآزYour smile still lingersظآز
ظآزYou are the brightest light
in my regretsظآز
I'll get you a fever reducer.
ظآزCan't find a cureظآز
ظآزTo love you after we've partedظآز
ظآزYou are the time I most want to keepظآز
ظآزThe future I strive toward
in the darknessظآز
Here.
ظآزHow I wish I could
give you my sunshineظآز
Are you still going to marry Xiao Jin?
We've already broken up.
Then could you give me a chance?
ظآزEvery star isظآز
ظآزMy heartbeat for youظآز
ظآزWant to ride the evening breezeظآز
ظآزAnd land in your armsظآز
ظآزThe starry sky is like your eyesظآز
ظآزIn the blue skyظآز
(Calm down.)
(Ji Xuan, you're here to thank him,
not to fall for him.)
(But why is my heart beating so fast?)
ظآزIn the vast sea of starsظآز
ظآزFlickering neon lightsظآز
ظآزLonging spreads
throughout the universeظآز
ظآزEvery star isظآز
ظآزMy heartbeat for youظآز
ظآزWant to ride the evening breezeظآز
ظآزAnd land in your armsظآز
ظآزThe starry sky is like your eyesظآز
ظآزIn the blue skyظآز
ظآزYour smile still lingersظآز
ظآزYou are the brightest light
in my regretsظآز
ظآزYou are the painful greeting
in my despairظآز
ظآزCan't find a cureظآز
ظآزTo love you after we've partedظآز
ظآزYou are the time I most want to keepظآز
ظآزThe future I strive toward
in the darknessظآز
ظآزSlowly getting closer to youظآز
ظآزHow I wish
I could give you my sunshineظآز
ظآزYou are the brightest light
in my regretsظآز
ظآزCan't find a cureظآز
ظآزTo love you after we've partedظآز
ظآزYou are the time I most want to keepظآز
ظآزThe future I strive toward
in the darknessظآز
ظآزSlowly getting closer to youظآز
ظآزHow I wish
I could give you my sunshineظآز